genji is with you
staying out of trouble genji
on my best behavior captain
how about a quick sparring session
you're on show me what you've been
working on
genji i heard you used to have all the
high scores here
that's right wait used to
hey where did they all go
doomfist you are truly a worthy foe
if we fight again i can't promise you'll
walk away this
time nor can i
it's been a while brother my brother is
dead
i killed him with my own hands
what's wrong hanzo don't you recognize
me
you may call yourself my brother but you
are not the genji are you
so this is what has become of you
a pity i will not be judged by you
it is not too late to change your course
brother you are mistaken brother
i am beyond redemption together
we could have built an empire so was
your dream
not mine we could have built an
empire together so was your dream
not mine you
will never amount to anything we shall
see
brother think you can do better than me
i am certain of it what would our father
think of what we've become brother
it's hard to say who he'd been more
disappointed by
any chocolates today brother those were
your
amusements not mine i
do not fear death no you
find living the challenge
and i thought i'd taken my licks i was a
reckless youth
but you are something else entirely
hey genji how about i hook up your
lights to my music
that is not what they're for
hey genji how about i hook up your
lights to my music
just this one time
you might be fast genji but you ain't
faster than a bullet
why don't we find out genji
how did you ever get used to you know
it was hard enough for me and it was
just the one arm it was a long and a
difficult road
but now i feel at ease in my own body
why have you come back to this place
mccree the only thing it ever is
unfinished business and unhappy history
how'd a guy like you get a nickname like
sparrow anyways
my father shojiro called me that as an
insult
i've grown to like it
you seem there genji i am a different
man now
i am whole i got you some chocolates
genji
swiss they're the best thank you angela
perhaps you could share them with me
angela
i have some chocolates for you not swiss
i suppose it will have to do thank you
genji
this reminds me of our time on base in
switzerland
you are the only one who stayed up so
late i enjoyed our conversations
angela what did you wish for onya
tanzaku
if i tell you does it mean it won't come
true
much more talkative now aren't you genji
i find the company
more agreeable these days i always
thought you would understand better than
most the duality of human existence
i am at peace with it i suspect
you will be forever unsatisfied
orisa you grow stronger each time i see
you
my artificial intelligence makes it
possible to learn from my experiences
and from everything i observe
you wouldn't believe what i learned
about you sparrow
i am at peace with who i was your threat
does not concern me
genji ready for some sparring practice
of course you are the only one i have
trouble
keeping up with what is it like to have
the chance to change the past
sometimes it doesn't want to change do
not blame yourself for monda's death
it was not your fault you don't
understand genji
i could have saved him maybe the world
would have been better
off if it had been me instead of him
genji this is just like old times
our paths cross for now as to the future
we shall see i always liked working with
you winston
no awkward small talk always liked
working with you too
you have a great sense of humor
how do i trust a man who is half machine
the heart of a man
still beats inside me how can i convince
you
that i am still a man i know what you
are
i'm only sorry that you do not
it is good to fight alongside one of my
brightest
pupils and you master
so this is where you grew up you must
show me around that was another life
does the suffering of the omnics here
trouble you master
it does my brother mandata gave much to
improve their lives
but it was not to be genji
how was your reunion with your brother
he is still not ready for time to flow
forward again
time is a river it may be stopped for a
while
but it will always flow the same
direction
i am victorious this time brother
mock death at your own peril i have the
upper hand this time
master shisho motion
i will avenge you brother master
angela winston tracer
bastion catch back at you brother
hi good aim mccree do you go i gotta
this is not a snowball fight think fast
farah rising hammer intercepting sword
cheers tracer just like in training
calm down winston in hindsight
i should have listened when hanzo said
he had the high ground